John B-PER
Smith I-PER
works O
at O
Google B-ORG
in O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC

Apple B-ORG
released O
a O
new O
iPhone O
today O

Mary B-PER
visited O
Paris B-LOC
last O
summer O
